I. Feinberg, Robert Arbitration Records 5548
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- [Case 190-199] Ibid. 6/26/56-9/4/57, 1956-1957 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  Issues: Rates of pay, case 190. Recall, case 191. Layoffs, seniority, case 192. Classification of jobs, rates of pay, case 193. Bargaining units, case 194. Medical release, case 195. Assignment of new jobs, assignment to work outside classification, cases
- [Case 200-209] Ibid. 10/4/57-9/19/58, 1957-1958 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  Issues: Layoffs, recall, case 200. Classification of jobs, merit increases and merit review, cases 201-203, 205-209. Layoffs, vacation pay, notice, case 204.
- [Case 210-214] Ibid. 9/19/58-3/20/59, 1958-1959 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  Issues: Classification of jobs, merit increases and merit review, cases 210- 212. Rates of pay, case 213. Suspension, discharge, theft, case 214.
- [Case 215] Ibid. 7/27/59, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  Issues: Classification of jobs, merit increases and merit review. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [Case 216] Ibid. 7/27/59, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- [Case 217] Bethlehem Steel Co. (Shipbuilding Div.) Quincy Yard, Quincy, Mass. And IUMSW, Local 5, CIO. 7/27/59, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- [Case 101-109] Bethlehem Steel Co. (Shipbuilding Div.) Staten Island Yard, Staten Island, N.Y. and Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, Local #12, CIO. 3/26/51-10/6/53, 1951-1953 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  Issues: Discharge, Improper work practices, case 101. Discharge, strikes, slowdowns and work stoppage, cases 102-103. Classification of jobs, merit increases and merit review, case 104. Plant rules, schedules of work, case 105. Suspension, strikes, slowdo
- [Case 110-119] Ibid. 10/16/53-2/1/54, 1953-1954 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  Issues: Compensation, crew size, cases 112, 118. Assignment to work outside classification, case 113. Classification of jobs, merit increases and merit review, case 114. Compensation, schedules of work, case 115. Reporting pay, case 116. Medical release,
- [Case 120-129] Ibid. 2/1/54-12/16/55, 1954-1955 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  Issues: Classification of jobs, merit increases and merit review, case 120. Compensation, layoffs, case 121. Reporting pay, case 122. Layoffs, seniority, case 123. Assignment to work outside classification. Case 124, 125, 129. Compensation, layoffs, overt
- [Case 130-134] Ibid. 5/20/58-8/29/58, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  Issues: Classification of jobs, merit increases and merit review, cases 130, 134. Layoffs, holiday pay, case 131. Suspension, standards of production, case 132. Suspension, tardiness, case 133.
- [Case 135] Bethlehem Steel Co. (Shipbuilding Div.) Staten Island Yard, Staten Island, N.Y. and IUMSW, Local #12, CIO. 4/13/59, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  Issues: Cost of living adjustments. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- [Case 136] Ibid. 1/15/60, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  Issues: Assignment to work outside classification. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- [Case 137] Ibid. 2/18/60, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  Issues: Layoffs, Assignment to work outside classification. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- [Case 138] Ibid. 2/18/60, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  Issues: Layoffs, seniority. Contains notes, and exhibits.
- [Case 139] Ibid. 2/29/60, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  Issues: Layoffs, removal of work from bargaining unit. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [Case 140] Ibid. 3/1/60, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  Issues: layoffs, assignment to work outside classification. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [Case 101-109] Bethlehem Steel Co. (Shipbuilding Div.) 27th Street Yard, Brooklyn, N.Y. and IUMSW, Local 13, CIO. 12/7/49-9/21/51, 1949-1951 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  Issues: Discrimination, case 101. Assignment of work outside of classification, case 102, 108. Crew size, case 103. Suspension, tardiness, case 104. Medical release, case 105. Layoffs, assignment of work outside classification, cases 106, 109. Removal of
- [Case 110-119] Ibid. 9/28/51-5/14/52, 1951-1952 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  Issues: Layoffs, equipment and physical facilities, case 110, 111. Assignment to work outside classification, cases 112, 115, 119. Elimination of jobs, case 113. Managements rights; employee requirements, case 114. Recall, seniority, case 116. Equipment a
- [Case 120-129] Ibid. 5/14/52-6/1/54, 1952-1954 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  Issues: Layoffs, equipment and physical facilities, case 120. Recall, seniority, case 121. Assignment to work outside classification, cases 122, 125, 128. Call-in pay, case 123. Rest period, case 124. Classification of jobs, merit increases and merit revi
- [Case 130-139] Bethlehem Steel Co. (Shipbuilding Div.) 27th Street Yard, Brooklyn, N.Y. and IUMSW, Local 13, CIO. 6/1/54-7/7/55, 1954-1955 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  Issues: Holiday pay, case 130. Layoffs, seniority, case 131. Assignment to work outside classification, cases 132, 139. Suspension, tardiness, lunch periods, case 133. Premium pay, cases 134, 135. Past practice, premium pay, case 136. Crew size, safety, c
- [Case 140-150] Ibid. 7/7/55-8/3/59, 1955-1959 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  Issues: Seniority, case 140. Super seniority, case 141. Crew size, safety, case 142. Premium pay, case 143. Merger, bargaining units, rates of pay, case 144, 150. Rates of pay, case 145. Assignment to work outside classification, cases 146, 147, 149. Layo
- [Case 101-109] Bethlehem Steel Co. (Shipbuilding Div.) 56th Street Yard, Brooklyn, N.Y. and IUMSW, Local #13, CIO 11/8/49-9/29/51, 1949-1951 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  Issues: Demotion, seniority, case 101. Promotion, seniority, case 102, layoffs, seniority, case 103, 105, 106, 107. Suspension, negligence and carelessness, case 104. Premium pay, case 108. Employer requirements, case 109.
- [Case 110-119] Ibid. 11/2/51-12/28/56, 1951-1956 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  Issues: Assignment to work outside classification, cases 110, 111, 117, 118. Holiday pay, case 112. Recall, seniority, case 113. Layoffs, seniority, case 114. Classification of jobs, premium pay, case 115. Call-in, case 116. Removal of work from the barga
- [Case 120-124] Ibid. 1/4/57-4/29/58, 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  Issues: Premium pay, case 120. Classification of jobs, merit increases and merit review, case 121. Assignment to work outside classification, cases 122, 124. Shift schedules, management rights, case 123.
- [Case 101-104] Bethlehem Steel Co. (Shipbuilding Div.) Hoboken Yard, Hoboken, N.J. and IUMSW, Local #15, CIO 5/10/54-4/25/58, 1954-1958 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  Issues: classification of jobs, rates of pay, case 101. Holiday pay, case 102. Shift scheduling, premium pay, case 103. Discharge, improper personal conduct, case 104.
- [Case 101-109] Bethlehem Steel Co. (Shipbuilding Div.) Baltimore Yard, Baltimore, Md. And IUMSW, Local #24, CIO. 2/13/50-8/5/55, 1950-1955 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  Issues: Layoffs, seniority, case 101. Assignment to work outside classification, cases 102, 104. Recall, cases 103, 108. Removal of work from the bargaining unit, supervisors and foremen, case 105. Demotion, incompetence and inefficiency, case 106. Classi
- [Case 110-112] Ibid. 8/5/55-7/2/59, 1955-1959 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  Issues: Suspensions, discharges, absences, case 110. Classification of jobs, merit increases and merit review, case 111, 112.
- [Case 101-109] Bethlehem - Sparrows Point Shipyard, Inc. and IUMSW, Local #33, CIO. 3/10/54-4/2/57, 1954-1957 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  Issues: Classification of jobs, rates of pay, case 101-104. Discipline, fights and altercations, case 105. Incentive pay and incentive systems, cases 106, 109. Recall, case 107. Recall, overtime, case 108.
- [Case 110-119] Ibid. 4/2/51-3/8/52, 1951-1952 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  Issues: Incentive pay and incentive systems, case 110. Medical release, case 111. Classification of jobs, rates of pay, cases 112, 113, 118. Equipment and physical facilities, case 114. Safety, equipment and physical facilities, case 115. Rates of pay, co
- [Case 120-129] Ibid. 3/8/52-1/13/56., 1952-1956 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  Issues: Safety, case 120. Classification of jobs, rates of pay, cases 121- 122, 128, 129. Layoffs, seniority, case 123. Layoffs, notice, case 124. Assignment of new jobs, compensation, 125. Transfers, seniority, case 126. Suspension, plant rules, case 127.
- [Case 130-139] Ibid. 1/13/56-11/5/56, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  Issues: Layoffs, case 130. Plant rules, case 131. Transfers, demotions, cases 132, 133. Classification of jobs, merit increase and merit review, case 154. Bumping, case 135. Assignment to work outside classification, layoffs, cases 136-139.
- [Case 140-149] Ibid. 3/8/57-10/28/59, 1957-1959 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  Issues: Suspension, insubordination, 140. Classification of jobs, merit increases and merit review, case 141, 147, 148. Employer requirements, assignment to work outside of classification, case 142. Suspension, discharge, insubordination, case 143. Incent
- [Case 150] Ibid. 11/6/59, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  Decision: Discharge, improper possession of company property. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [Case 151] Ibid. 11/30/59, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  Decision: Call-in, past practice. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [Case 1-9] Bethlehem Steel Co. (Shipbuilding Div.) Quincy Yard, Quincy, Mass. And IUMSW, Local 90, CIO (Called Independent Union of Fore River Workers prior to and including case #5) 3/30/53-4/15/54, 1953-1954 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  Issues: Rates of pay, overtime, case1. Classification of jobs, merit increases and merit review, cases 2-7, 9. Holiday pay, case 8.
- [Case 10-18] Ibid. 4/15/54-11/30/56, 1954-1956 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  Issues: Classification of jobs, merit increases and merit review, cases 10, 12, 14, 16-18. Assignment to work outside classification, case 11, 15. Vacations and vacation pay, case 13.
- [Case 19] Ibid. 3/16/60, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  Decision: Premium pay, workweek, schedules of work. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [Case 20] Ibid. 3/16/60, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  Decision: Classification of jobs, merit increases and merit review. Contains notes and exhibits.
- Ibid. 3/16/60, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  Decision: Compensation, employee rights, absences. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [C1950] Bethlehem Correspondence, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- [C1951] Bethlehem Correspondence, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- [C1952] Bethlehem Correspondence, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- [C1953] Bethlehem Correspondence, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- [C1954] Bethlehem Correspondence, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- [C1955] Bethlehem Correspondence, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- [C1956-1959] Bethlehem Correspondence, 1956-1959, Hotel & Railroad Bills. (Box 34, Folder 7)
- [Case 2602-1] Bethlehem Steel Co. and USA, Local #2602, Lackawanna 1/19/62 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  Decision: Incentive pay and incentive system, past practice. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [Case 2602-2] Ibid. 1/19/62 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  Decision: Lockout, compensation. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [Case 2602-3] Ibid. 2/15/62, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  Decision: Overtime, workweek. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [Case 2602-4] Ibid. 3/14/62, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- [Case 2602-5] Ibid. 3/14/52, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- [Case 2602-6] Ibid. 3/30/62, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  Decision: Assignment to work outside classification.
- [Case 2602-7] Ibid. 3/30/62, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  Decision: Assignment to work outside classification. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [Case 2602-8] Ibid. 4/24/62, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  Decision: Temporary vacancies. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [Case 2602-9] Ibid. 4/24/62, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  Decision: Promotion, seniority, ability. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [2602-10] Ibid. 4/24/62, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  Decision: Assignment of work outside classification.
- [2602-11] Ibid. 5/21/62, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  Decision: Transfers, vacancies. Contains notes, and exhibits.
- [2602-12] Various Lackawanna grievances settled or withdrawn before/during arbitration (Box 34, Folder 19)
- [Case 2602-13] Lackawanna correspondence. (Box 34, Folder 20)
- [Case 2602-14] Miscellaneous information on the Lackawanna plant and facilities. (Box 34, Folder 21)
- [WES 1] William Simkin Decisions - Local 5 Decisions 1-15. 12/26/46-6/9/47, 1946-1947 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- [WES 2] Ibid. Decisions 16-30. 7/10/47-6/17/48, 1947-1948 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- [WES 3] Ibid. Decisions 31-45A. 6/17/48-12/24/48, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- [WES 4] Ibid. Decisions 46A-65A. 12/24/48-7/5/49, 1948-1949 (Box 34, Folder 25)
- [WES 5] William E. Simkin Decisions - Local 12 Decisions 1-17A. 4/11/46-7/13/48, 1946-1948 (Box 34, Folder 26)
- [WES 6] Ibid. Decisions 18A-44B. 7/13/48-8/13/54, 1948-1954 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- [WES 7] William E. Simkin Decisions - Local 13 (27th Street Yard) Decisions 1-22. 2/16/45-4/12/47, 1945-1947 (Box 34, Folder 28)
- [WES 8] Ibid. 23-43A. 4/12/47-7/23/49, 1947-1949 (Box 34, Folder 29)
- [WES 9] William E. Simkin Decisions - Local 13, (56th Street Yard) Decisions 2-14. 3/19/45-7/23/49, 1945-1949 (Box 34, Folder 30)
- [WES 10] William E. Simkin Decisions - Local 15 Decisions 1-9A. 4/20/25-6/10/48, 1925-1948 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- [WES 11] William E. Simkin Decisions - Local 24 Decisions 1-15. 8/12/46-2/26/48, 1946-1948 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- [WES 12] Ibid. Decisions 16-30A. 2/26/48-7/17/53, 1948-1953 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- [WES 13] Ibid. Decisions 31A-45B. 7/17/53-2/8/54, 1953-1954 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- [WES 14] Ibid. Decisions 46B-67B. 2/8/54-8/5/54, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- [WES 15] William E. Simkin Decision - Local 25 Decisions 1-7. 11/22/46-4/1/47 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- [WES 16] William E. Simkin Decisions - Local 33 Decisions 1-15 12/12/45-6/10/47 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- [WES 17] Ibid. Decisions 16-30A. 1/17/47-2/20/53, 1947-1953 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- [WES 18] Ibid. Decisions 13A-43A. 2/20/53-5/25/53, 1953 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- [WES 19] Ibid. Decisions 46A-60A. 5/25/53-8/28/53, 1953 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- [WES 20] Ibid. Decisions 61A-75B. 8/28/53-3/18/54, 1953-1954 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- [WES 21] Ibid. Decisions 76B-96B. 3/18/54-1/7/54, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- [WES 22] William E. Simkin Decisions - Local 43 Decisions 1-14. 7/10/45-4/4/47, 1945-1947 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- [WES 23] William E. Simkin Decisions - "S" Notation Decisions S1-S21. 9/30/55-4/9/56, 1955-1956 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- [WES 24] Ibid. Decisions S22-S40. 4/9/56-1/25/57, 1956-1957 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- [WES 25] Ibid. Decisions S41-S60. 1/25/57-6/7/67, 1957-1967 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- [WES 26] Ibid. Decisions S61-S85. 6/19/57-9/29/58, 1957-1958 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- [WES 27] Ibid. S86-S103. 10/3/58-9/8/60, 1958-1960 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- [RTS 1] Ralph T. Seward Decisions. Decisions 1000-1001. 4/7/52-5/1/52, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- [MMS 1] Mitchell M. Shipman Decisions. Decisions 1-7. 12/8/44-12/4/45, 1944-1945 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- [SW 1] Saul Wallen Decisions. Decisions 500-513. 9/21/50-10/23/50, 1950 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- [M 1] Miscellaneous Bethlehem Decisions (Box 35, Folder 22)
- [F1] A.B.C. Fur Co. 1/12/70, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  Decision: crew size; contractual duties. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [F2] Murray Abrams Furs, Inc., 1972-1974 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  Decisions: 1) 9/5/72, Vacation pay; successor company. 2) 10/23/74 Employee rights.
- [F3] Abrams & Davis, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  Decisions: 1) 11/5/69. Supervisors and foremen; improper personal conduct. Contains notes. 2) 3/17/70. Vacation pay; Successor company. 3) 3/18/70. Holiday pay. Contains notes. 4) 4/9/71. Vacation pay. Contains notes. 5) 5/7/70. Sick leave and sick pay.
- [F4] Addison Furs Ltd., 1971-1973 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  Decisions: 1) 3/3/71. Vacation pay. 2) 7/11/73. Vacation pay.
- [F5] Max Adelman Furs Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  Decisions: 1) 4/21/70. Discharge; quits. Contains notes. 2) 3/31/70. Vacation pay; holiday pay. Contains notes. 3) 4/1/71. Union security. Contains notes. 4) 4/13/71. Union security. Contains notes. 5) 11/3/71. Vacation pay; holiday pay.
- [F6] Alderman Fur Corp. 2/5/69, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  Decision: Vacation pay
- [F7] Alsey Schwartz, Inc., 1971-1973 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  Decisions: 1) 2/3/71. Vacation pay; holiday pay. 2) 4/21/71. Holiday pay. Contains notes. 3) 7/1/71. Leaves of absences. Contains notes. 4) 9/8/71. Contracting out. 5) 2/28/73. Overtime. Contains notes.
- [F8] Anderson & Reventlow, Inc., 1970-1973 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  Decisions: 1) 1/28/70. Holiday pay; vacation pay. 2) 9/4/71. Removal of work from the bargaining unit. Contains notes. 3) 2/3/71. Vacation pay; Holiday pay. 4) 10/6/71. Vacation pay; back pay award. 5) 10/20/71. Rates of pay. 6) 3/22/72. Holiday pay; vaca
- [F9] Anfanger & Eisner Furs, Inc., 1970 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  Decisions: 1) 5/25/70. 2) 5/25/70. Fights and altercations. Both contain notes.
- [F10] Angeli's Fur Co., 1968-1969 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  Decisions: 1) 5/3/68. Employer associations. Contains notes. 2) 7/28/69. Removal of work from the bargaining unit; Contractual duties. Contains notes.
- [F11] Anita Furs Ltd., 1971-1973 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  Decisions: 1) 2/2/71. Holiday pay; Vacation pay. Contains notes. 2) 2/21/73. Holiday pay; Vacation pay.
- [F12] Antonovich Bros., Inc., 1970-1973 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  Decisions: 1) 9/1/70. Vacation pay. Contains notes. 2) 4/14/71. Overtime. 3) 10/26/71. Supervisors and foremen; Crew size. Contains notes. 4) 3/22/72. Contracting out. 5) 11/2/72. Contracting out. Contains notes. 6) 7/25/73. Crew size; Interpretation of p
- [F13] Arbeit Bros., Inc., 1971-1973 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  Decisions: 1) 12/30/71. Quits. Contains notes. 2) 5/31/73. Discharge; insubordination. Contains notes.
- [F14] Arm & Goodman, Inc., 1973 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  Decisions: 1) 2/1/73. Discharge; Insubordination. Contains notes. 2) 5/31/73. Discharge; Insubordination. Contains notes.
- [F15] Aron, Bauer & Weisman, Inc. 1/23/69, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  Decision: rates of pay; holiday pay; vacation pay. Contains notes.
- [F16] Artal Furs, Inc., 1972-1974 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  Decisions: 1) 9/25/72. Union representative and business; supervisors and foremen. Contains notes. 2) 9/25/74. Vacation pay. 3) 12/4/74. Holiday pay; vacation pay.
- [F17] Morris Bader & Sons Corp., 1968-1971 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  Decisions: 1) 9/9/68. Crew size. Contains notes. 2) 3/5/70 Crew size. Contains notes. 3) 3/31/71. Vacation pay.
- [F18] Baker Merchandising Corp. 2/24/71, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  Decision: Contracting out.
- [F19] Barlan Furs, Inc., 1968-1974 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  Decisions: 1) 5/2/68. Overtime. 2) 5/3/68. Union representative and business. 3) 7/8/70. Leave of absence. Contains notes. 4) 6/26/74. Sick leave and sick pay. Contains notes. 5) 7/25/74. Sick leave and sick pay. Contains notes.
- [F20] Baron-Jackman, Inc. 10/4/73, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  Decision: Discharge; tardiness; improper work practices.
- [F21] Baws Bros. Inc. 6/14/73, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  Decision: Discharge; fights and altercations. Contains notes.
- [F22] Bensam Furs, Inc., 1972 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  Decisions: 1) 11/16/72. Quits. Contains notes and exhibits. 2) 2/3/72. Termination of business; compensation. Contains notes.
- [F23] Berche Fur Co. 3/27/74, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- [F24] Nat Berg, Inc., 1974 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  Decisions: 1) 5/1/74. Recall. 2) 12/4/74. Holiday pay; Vacation pay.
- [F25] Bergdorf Goodman Fur Corp. 7/17/72, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  Decision: Sick leave and sick pay. Contains notes.
- [F26] Henry Berger Fashion, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  Decisions: 5/7/70. Holiday pay. Contains notes. 2) 2/11/71. Recall. Contains notes.
- [F27] Henry Berger Furs, Inc. 10/22/68, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  Decisions: Call-in. Contains notes.
- [F28] M&E Berger, Inc. 5/21/75, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  Decision: reduction in force. Contains notes.
- [F29] Marvin Berger. 12/24/68, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  Decision: Refusal to pay. Contains notes.
- [F30] R&R Berger, Inc., 1968-1970 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  Decisions: 1) 4/26/68. Call-in. 2) 6/17/70. Sick leave and sick pay.
- [F31] Berger & Savage, Inc., 1970-1974 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  Decisions: 1) 10/27/70. Discharge; alcoholism, drinking and intoxication. Contains notes and exhibits. 2) 2/3/71. Holiday pay; Vacation pay. 3) 10/6/71. Assignment of jobs. Contains notes. 4) 10/31/71. Contracting out. 5) 10/27/71. Contracting out. 6) 3/2
- [F32] Berkowitz, Smith & Milbrod, Inc. 1/29/69, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 32)
- [F33] Berman Bros. 5/19/72 (Box 36, Folder 33)
- [F34] Carl Bernstein & Jasnow, Inc.1/29/69, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  Decision: Holiday pay; vacation pay. Contains notes.
- [F35] David Bernstein, Inc. 10/23/68, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  Decision: Removal of work from the bargaining unit; supervisors and foremen.
- [F36] Bernstein & Slatkin, Inc. 9/5/69, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  Decision: Employer-Union relations; employer associations. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [F37] Biegeleisen & Schour, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  Decisions: 1) 1/5/71. Holiday pay; vacation pay. 2) 2/3/71. Discharge; termination of business. 3) 2/11/71. Interpretation of past arbitration award; damages.
- [F38] Birken Bros. 2/3/69, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  Decision: Vacation pay.
- [F39] Birnbaum & Willner, Inc., 1969-1974 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  Decisions: 1) 1/22/69. Overtime. 2) 7/15/70. Leaves of absence. Contains notes. 3) 12/4/74. Holiday pay; vacation pay. Contains exhibits.
- [F40] Blau & Morson, Inc. 4/26/68, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  Decision: Vacations and vacation pay. Contains notes.
- [F41] Blander Fur Corp., 1972 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  Decisions: 1) 10/20/72. Strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages. Contains notes. 2) 9/8/72. Holiday pay; vacation pay. Contains notes. 3) 9/8/72. Discharge; termination of business. Contains notes.
- [F42] Blatt & Gordon. 9/27/74, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  Decision: Leaves of absence. Contains notes.
- [F43] Blum & Fink, 1971-1972 (Box 36, Folder 43)
  Decision: 1) 6/30/71. Discharge; falsification. Contains notes and exhibits. 2) 10/5/72. Assignment of jobs. Contains notes.
- [F44] Allan Borack, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  Decisions: 1) 4/9/69. Reduction in force. 2) 6/18/69. Discharge; Improper personal conduct. 3) 3/23/70. Vacation pay.
- [F45] Samuel Braun Furs, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 45)
  Decisions: 1) 9/25/72. Vacation pay. Contains notes. 2) 9/20/73. Overtime
- [F46] Nathan Brecher & Son, Inc., 1971-1974 (Box 36, Folder 46)
  Decisions: 1) 3/3/71. Holiday pay; vacation pay. 2) 5/25/71. Files; compensation. Contains notes. 3) 3/27/74. Rates of pay. Contains notes. 4) 5/6/74. Layoffs; ability. Contains notes
- [F47] Breslin-Baker, Inc., 1970 (Box 36, Folder 47)
  Decisions: 1) 2/4/70. Overtime. 2) 10/28/70. Files.
- [F48] Brodlie & Buckberg, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 36, Folder 48)
  Decisions: 1) 1/23/69. Leaves of absence. Contains notes. 2) 4/1/70. Holiday pay.
- [F49] Brooklyn & N.Y. Fur Mfg. Co., Inc. 1/3/73, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 49)
- [F50] Edward Brown Furs, Inc., 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 50)
  Decisions: 1) 3/14/73. Reduction in force. 2) 8/14/73. Reduction in force. Contains notes. 3) 5/22/74. Rates of pay; refusal to pay. 4) 5/22/74. Rates of pay; holiday pay; vacation pay. 5) 6/26/74. Rates of pay.
- [F51] Harry Brown, Inc., 1971 (Box 36, Folder 51)
  Decisions: 1) 5/19/71. Files. Contains notes. 2) 7/1/71. Interpretation of past arbitration award; files. Contains notes. 3) 10/13/71. Contracting out.
- [F52] Sam & Leo Brown, Inc. 3/27/74, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 52)
  Decision: rates of pay.
- [F53] Camelot Furs, Inc. 1/28/69, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 53)
  Decision: Vacation pay. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [F54] Canadian Fur Trappers Corp., 1971-1972 (Box 36, Folder 54)